{
  "numOfQs": 10,
  "title": "Human Body Quiz",
  "quizitems": [{
    "questiontext":"Where in the body is the scapular muscle?",
    "answertext":"Shoulder",
    "choices":["Knee",    
     "Shoulder",
     "Head",
     "Arm"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What is the name of the only bone in the body not connected to another?",
    "answertext":"Hyoid",
    "choices":["Axis",    
     "Ulna",
     "Femur",
     "Hyoid"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"According to the Red Cross what is the most common Blood Type?",
    "answertext":"Blood Type O",
    "choices":["Blood Type A",    
     "Blood Type O",
     "Blood Type B",
     "Blood type AB"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What is the smallest bone in the human body?",
    "answertext":"Stapes",
    "choices":["Stapes",    
     "Pinna",
     "Clavicle",
     "Fibula"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"How much does an average human heart weigh?",
    "answertext":"Approx. 250gm-300grams - female & 300-350 grams-male",
    "choices":["Approx. 250gm-300grams - female & 300-350 grams-male",    
     "Approx. 350-450grams female and 500-600gram male",
     "Approx. 100-150grams female and 200-250grams male",
     "Approx. 600-700gram female and 800-900grams male"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"Where in the body is the thyroid gland found?",
    "answertext":"Neck",
    "choices":["Stomach",    
     "Underarm",
     "Neck",
     "Head"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What is the knee-jerk reflex called?",
    "answertext":"Patella Reflex",
    "choices":["Patella Reflex",    
     "Humerus Reflex",
     "Coccyx Reflex",
     "Illium Reflex"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"True or False – Can the body generate new brain cells?",
    "answertext":"Yes",
    "choices":["Yes",    
     "No",
     "Sometimes",
     "In some people"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What Body system do the Skin, hair and nails belong to?",
    "answertext":"Integumentary System",
    "choices":["Circulatory System",    
     "Skeletal System",
     "Integumentary System",
     "Digestive System"]
  },
  {
    "questiontext":"What Body Part changes the least throughout a person’s life?",
    "answertext":"Eyes",
    "choices":["Ears",    
     "Nose",
     "Eyes",
     "Tongue"]
  }]   
}